A Guide to the Davison Fund, Inc. records (II) FA080
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Declinations, 1923-1942; 3
  - Institute - Inter-Denominational, 1935-1942 (Box 23, Folder 185)
    Institute for Propaganda Analysis, Institute for the Crippled and Disabled, Institute of Engineering Practice, Institute of Student Aid, Institution for the Chinese Blind, Inter-Church Youth Center, Inter-Denominational Committee for Religious Education on Release Time, Inter-Denominational Institute for Negro Ministers, Inter-Denominational Summer Institute for Ministers
  - International Migration Service, 1938-1939 (Box 24, Folder 186)
  - International (S) (Box 24, Folder 187)
    International Society for Christian Endeavor, International Student Service
  - J-M, 1935-1940 (Box 24, Folder 188)
    Joint Vocational Service, Kagawa's Rural Work, Kambini Training School, League of Composers, League of Fair Play, Life Camps, Lingnan University, Madras Christian College, Maine Council of Religious Education, Medical Administration Service, Inc., Missionary Medical College for Women
  - Nanking - National (A), 1934-1936 (Box 24, Folder 189)
    Nanking Theological Seminary, National Alliance of Art and Industry
  - National (B-P), 1932-1940 (Box 24, Folder 190)
    National Bureau for the Advancement of Music, National Christian Councils, National Probation Association
  - Nav - New (S), 1935-1939 (Box 24, Folder 191)
    Navajo House of Religion, Near East College Association, Near East Foundation, New School for Social Research
  - New (Y) - Nursing, 1935-1940 (Box 24, Folder 192)
    New York Association for the Blind, New York Baseball Federation, New York Mission Society, New York Colored Mission Society, Northern Baptist Convention, Ministers and Missionaries Benefit, Nursing Service Center of Westchester County
  - O-R, 1933-1938 (Box 24, Folder 193)
    Omi Brotherhood; Presbyterian Theological Seminary; Prison Association of New York; Rayher, Edward R.; Reformed Church in America - Board of Foreign Missions; Ashran for Women at Vellore; Relief Society to the Aged
  - Sai-Sca, 1934-1942 (Box 25, Folder 194)
    Saint Christopher's Training College; Saint Luke's International Catholic Church; Saint Thomas Liberal Catholic Church; Saint Vincent's Hospital, New York City; Scarritt College for Christian Workers
  - Sch-Soc, 1934-1940 (Box 25, Folder 195)
    Schauffler School School of Art League, School of Applied Religion, Servants of India, Shanghai American School, Social Work Publicity Council
  - Sol-Stu, 1934-1939 (Box 25, Folder 196)
    Soldiers and Sailors Club of New York, Student Christian Movement, Student Christian Movement of Great Britain and Ireland, Student Christian Movement of New York State
  - U, 1923-1939 (Box 25, Folder 197)
    Union Christian Hospital, Pyengyang, Korea; Union Churches of Tokyo; Union Settlement; Union Theological Seminary, Foochow, China; Union Theological Seminary, Manila, Philippines; United Church of Manila; United Neighborhood Houses of New York, Inc.; United Parents Association of New York City; Universal School of Handicrafts
  - V, 1937-1941 (Box 25, Folder 198)
    Vanderbilt University School of Religion, Vidyodaya Residential School for Girls, Visual Religion
  - Westchester - World (C), 1935-1940 (Box 25, Folder 199)
    Westchester Cancer Committee Westchester County Conference on Group Visiting Nurses Westchester County Federation for Women's Clubs Westchester County Girl Scouts, Inc. Westchester Institute of Fine Arts Women's Christian College, Madras, India World Congress of Faiths
  - World (D) - World's, 1936-1938 (Box 25, Folder 200)
    World Dominion Movement World's Alliance of Young Mens Christian Associations (YMCA)
  - Y, 1935-1941 (Box 25, Folder 201)
    Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - Brooklyn, Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - World Council, Youth Builders, Inc.
- Davison Fund Index, 4; 5 box(es) 5 boxes 4x6x12 inches each.
  General
  The Davison Fund index provides indexing to correspondence, appropriations, declinations, and minutes. The index includes entries for personal names and organizations, but not subjects or places.
  Arrangement
  The index is arranged in 4 series of index cards: Correspondence, Appropriations, Declinations, and Minutes. Each series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Correspondence Index
    Scope and Contents
    Provides indexing to correspondence found in the Davison Funds's Series 2: Appropriations files.
    - A - G (Box 26)
    - H - Q (Box 27)
    - R - Z (Box 28)
  - Appropriations Index
    - A - Z (Box 28)
  - Declinations Index
    - A - Z (Box 29)
  - Minutes Index
    - A - Z (Box 29)
  - Unidentified Index
    Cards include headings for organizations, but are otherwise blank.
    - A - Z (Box 30)